You were born here. Raised here.
-- 你在這裡出生，長大。
This dome is the only world you've ever known.
-- 這個圓頂是你所認識的唯一世界。
There's a place just off past the eastern ridge. Right there.
-- 在東邊山脈的遠處有個地方，就在那裡。
Dad, what are you talking about?
-- 爸，你在說什麼？
You'll see.
-- 你會明白的。
Get out there.
-- 去那裡。
To the crater.
-- 去那個隕石坑。
Whatever's out there,
-- 無論有什麼，
your dad wants you to see it.
-- 你爸爸希望你去看看。
We've never even been outside the dome before.
-- 我們從未去過圓頂之外。
So what's it going to be?
-- 你們決定怎麼做？
We're leaving tonight.
-- 我們今晚就出發。
I hear she's weird.
-- 我聽說她很奇怪。
Why?
-- 為什麼？
She's from Earth.
-- 她來自地球。
So? They're peculiar.
-- 那又怎樣？他們很奇特。
You're peculiar.
-- 你也很奇特。
All in favor？
-- 大家都贊成嗎？
Let's go steal a rover.
-- 讓我們去偷一輛月球車。
The lockdown will commence...
-- 封鎖措施即將啟動...
Come on.
-- 快點。
...in five...
-- ...五...
...four...
-- ...四...
...three...
-- ...三...
...two...
-- ...二...
...one.
-- ...一。
You know the best thing about road trips?
-- 你知道公路旅行最好的事情嗎？
You get to leave everything behind.
-- 你可以把一切都拋在腦後。
Here it is,
-- 到了，
bottom of the ninth... the wind up.
-- 九局末... 準備投球。
The sky on Earth. Is it really blue?
-- 地球上的天空，真的是藍色的嗎？
Yeah.
-- 是的。
Wow.
-- 哇。
The most important thing to remember...
-- 最重要的是要記住...
This is a bad idea.
-- 這是個糟糕的主意。
Watch out! Watch out!
-- 小心！小心！
It's not just about where you're going.
-- 重點不只在於目的地
Meteor shower!
-- 流星雨！
Addison! Run!
-- Addison！快跑！
It's about how you get there.
-- 重要的是前往的過程
The people you get there with.
-- 和同行的夥伴
Caleb, what's in the crater?
-- Caleb，坑洞裡有什麼？
I don't know.
-- 我不知道
Guess we'll find out.
-- 猜猜看，我們會發現什麼
You guys go first.
-- 你們先去
You're never quite the same as you were when you began.
-- 完成旅程後，你會不同於出發時的自己
These were the best two days of my life.
-- 這是我一生中最美好的兩天